(Sheldon:)Now, why don't you
accept my apology,
(Sheldon:)receive your free T-shirt, uh...
(Sheldon:)I hope extra small is okay.
(Sheldon:)For some reason
Wolowitz took a medium.
(Emily:)Well, I don't
accept your apology.
(Raj:)What are you doing?
(Emily:)It's called standing
up for myself.
(Emily:)You should try it some time.
(Raj:)Fine, how about this?
(Raj:)You're making me
uncomfortable by prolonging
(Raj:)this ridiculous fight,
and I wish you'd stop.
(Emily:)Oh, you want me to stop?
(Emily:)No problem.
(Raj:)No, come on,
please don't leave!
(Sheldon stammers)
(Sheldon:)Point of clarification...
are you still going on the trip?
(Sheldon:)Because if not...
(Emily:)Don't worry, you're good.
(Sheldon:)I caused that fight,
I feel terrible.
(stammers)
Wait, I can do that better...
(Sheldon:)I caused that fight.
(Sheldon:)I feel terrible.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, wow, I don't know
which one I like more.
(Penny:)So, was the fight
really bad?
(stammers)
No.
(Sheldon:)As a fight, it was excellent.
(Sheldon:)She used harsh language
and slammed the door.